片名：《無敵浩克》
(HULK GROWLING)
（爆炸震驚校園）
（卡爾沃大學實驗室的神秘事故）
（目擊到綠色怪物）
（現場找回實驗室器材）
（目標逃脫追捕）
（驚現綠色怪獸）
（採購請求：美國陸軍：斯塔克工業批准 註：《鋼鐵俠》主角開的那個軍工企業）
（截獲消息：伊麗莎白·羅斯博士於2006.2.7與班納聯繫）
（搜捕仍在繼續）
（他還在逃往嗎？）
（已經五個月沒有消息）
已經158天沒有事故發生
Is it ready?
可以吃了吧？
《簡明葡英詞典》
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Hey! That's a great punch.
嗨！打得好啊
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
餓了？
餓了
我們開始練呼吸
這裏，感情
(IN ENGLISH) Fear no good.So emotion and control.
恐懼不是好事，所以要控制感情
用你的橫膈膜呼吸（位於胸腔與腹部之間）
控制憤怒最好的辦法
就是控制你的身體
控制你的脈搏
Breathe. Breathe.
呼吸，呼吸
呼吸
Wait.
等等
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Okay.
好了
I can make it work for a while,but you need...
我可以讓它在工作一陣子，不過你得…
我得蓋間新工廠
Okay. Okay.
好的，好的
這五個月多虧你了
你這麼聰明，不該來做臨時工
我給你正式工資吧
Shut that off! Turn it off!
關掉！關掉！
Watch out!
讓開！
(SHOUTING IN PORTUGUESE)
Okay!
好了！
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(MAN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
想和我一起吃午飯嗎？
滾開，美國佬
想打架啊？
太晚了
別讓我…餓
我要是餓了，你不會…
好過的
That's not right.
好像說錯了
(SHOUTING IN PORTUGUESE)
(CHATTERING IN PORTUGUESE)
Oh, you.
噢，多謝
(SHOUTING IN PORTUGUESE)
You see that? See that?My ticket out of here.
看看，看見沒？我就要能離開這裏了
加密中，進度：100% 呼叫藍先生
藍，你在嗎？
綠先生！
很高興聽到你的消息，神秘的朋友！
我找到了
終於等到了
很漂亮的小花，是吧？
記住要多用點劑量，祝你好運:)
Damn it!
該死！
又失敗了
:(你用了多少？
全部
看來該見面了
不安全
你都伽瑪中毒了，同樣不安全
別再找花了
把血樣寄給我
否則幫不了你了
藍先生，紐約
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
阿靈頓，弗吉尼亞
SPARR: Here's something a bit more interesting.
這個也許會更有意思點
It's a possible gamma sickness. Milwaukee.
該病例我們懷疑是伽瑪中毒暈厥在密爾沃基市
A man drank one of those guarana sodas.
一名男子喝了瓜拉那飲料（能刺激神經的功能性植物，產於南美）
Guess it had a little more kick than he was looking for.
但他得到的能量有點過頭了
Wow.
哇
- Where was it bottled? - Porto Verde, Brazil.
- 飲料在哪裏灌裝的？ - 巴西的波多韋德
Have our people look for a white man at the bottling plant.
讓我們的探員去飲料廠找一名白人男子
Tell them no contact!If he even sees them, he's gone!
告訴他們不要接觸他！否則他會消失！
佛特·約翰遜，大沼澤地
I got you who I could.Short notice, but they're all quality.
我盡力了，時間倉促，不過這些都是精英
And I pulled you one ace.
而且還有一個殺手鑭
Emil Blonsky.Born in Russia, raised in England.
艾米·布朗斯基，生於俄國，在英國長大
And on loan to SOCOM from the Royal Marines.
是從皇家海軍借調到海豹突擊隊的
GENERAL: I know you cashed in some chips for this, Joe.
我知道你給了我一些得力干將，喬
Glad I could help. Just make it good.
很高興能幫助你，要就要最好的
SPARR: This is the target and the location.Snatch and grab, live capture.
這是目標和地點，要捉活的
You'll have your dart clips and suppression ordnance,
你們可以用釘槍和神經抑制彈
but live fire is for backup only.
但是實彈只能在支援的時候使用
We got local out there,but we want it tight and quiet.
我們在當地有駐點 不過要做得盡可能安靜
Is he a fighter?
他是個戰士嗎？
Your target is a fugitive from the US government
你的目標是美國政府通緝的
who stole military secrets.
竊取軍事機密的逃犯
He is also implicated in the deaths of two scientists,
同時他還害死了兩名科學家
a military officer, an Idaho state trooper and possibly two Canadian hunters.
一位軍官，一位愛達荷州傘兵 可能還有兩名加拿大獵人
So don't wait to see if he's a fighter!
所以別管他是不是戰士！
Tranq him and bring him back.
把他麻醉了提回來
(LAPTOP BLEEPS)
（加密的呼入消息）好消息
血樣初步檢測結果顯示 伽瑪水平已明顯下降
能治好我嗎？
能
不過…我需要更多數據
Oh, come on.
不是吧
暴露程度、伽瑪粒子濃度、細胞飽和度
不可能，數據不在這裏
那在哪裏？
在家
Camera.
探頭
Here we go.
進去
Get rid of the damn dog.
把那只該死的狗甩掉
Take him!
上！
Target's on the move.
目標在移動
Where is he?
他在哪兒？
He's on the ground.
他在地面
- Let's go! - COMMANDO: Go!
- 我們上！ - 上！
Move, move!
快，快！
謝謝
Go, go, go!
上,上,上！
Go! Go!
快,快!
Clear everyone out!
掃清路面！
Do not lose him!
別跟丟了！
Oh! No!
哦！不！
Get around behind him!
從後面包圍他！
Target moving past mobile unit 0-9-0.
目標經過090戰士的坐標
Oh, no.
哦，不是吧
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
You got to be kidding me.
玩笑開大了
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(MAN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Where is he? - Target acquired.
- 他在哪裏？  - 目標鎖定
MAN: Gringo!
美國佬！
(MAN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Let's go.
上
(MEN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
No!
不！
BRUCE: Please! No!
不！請別這樣！
Not the computer!
別搶電腦！
Gimme that! No!
給我！不！
現在怎麼不硬了，嗯？
再耍耍那些招數啊
來啊
請別這樣
我…憤怒…
很嚴重
(IN ENGLISH) You bad angry, G?I very bad angry.
你不好的生氣，美國佬？我很不好的生氣
Oh, no.
哦不
You don't understand! Something really bad is about to happen here!
你不明白！事情會一發不可收拾！
是啊，很嚴重
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(MAN LAUGHING)
(WHISPERING) Anybody else seeing this?
有人見過這個嗎？
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(HULK ROARING)
(FEEDBACK ON RADIO)
COMMANDO 1: We've got a bogey of some kind. Please advice.
有妖怪，請指示
That is the target!Use every tranq you've got!
那就是目標！用各種麻醉劑！
Do it now!
馬上動手！
(FIRING)
Go live! Go live! Go live!
用實彈，用實彈！
COMMANDO 1: Move! COMMANDO 2: Get out of the way!
- 快跑！  - 別擋著！
No!
不！
(HULK GROWLING)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
COMMANDO 2: It's behind us! Move! Move!
它在我們後面！快跑！
COMMANDO 1: Get him!
抓住它！
Shoot!
開槍！
(HULK GROWLS)
HULK: Leave me alone.
離我遠點
(GROWLING)
(HULK GRUNTING)
No! No!
不！不！
(HULK ROARING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
I knew something was different before I got the shot off.
我知道開槍之前肯定發生了什麼事
He had it on him when he bolted.
他逃跑的時候帶著這個
Is that a girlfriend? She helps him, maybe?
女朋友？也許她在幫助他？
She is no longer a factor.
不用考慮她了
We closed that door to him a long time ago.He's alone.
這事早就結束了，他就一個人
He wants to be alone.But see if he's been talking to anybody.
他想一個人呆著不過得查查他有沒有和別人聯繫
Forgive me, sir?
打擾了一下，長官？
Doesn't anybody want to talk about what went down in there? 'Cause...
您不想解釋一下當時的情況？因為…
He didn't lose us.
我們沒有被他甩掉
And he was not alone, sir. We had him.
他不是一個人，長官，我們盯住他了
And then something hit us, something...
然後我們被一個東西攻擊了，一個…
Something big hit us!
很龐大的東西！
It threw a forklift truck like it was a softball!
叉車對它來說就像是一個壘球
It was the most powerful thing I've ever seen.
那是我見過的最強大的生物
Well, it's gone.
不過，它已經消失了
Well, if Banner knows what it is,
但要是班納知道那是什麼
I'm gonna track him down,I'm gonna put my foot on his throat
我一定會抓到他，踩著他的喉嚨
- and I'm gonna... - That was Banner.
- 然後…  - 那就是班納
It
它
was Banner.
就是班納
- You have to explain that statement, sir. - No, I don't.
- 您得跟我說清楚，長官  - 算了吧
You've done a good job.
你幹的很漂亮
Pack up and get our men on a plane.We're going home.
讓大家收拾收拾上飛機，我們要回去了
已經1天沒有事故
Wait.
停車
Please.
拜託
能幫我嗎？
我不會說葡萄牙語
(IN ENGLISH) Where am I?
我這是在哪兒？（英語）
我這是在哪兒？（西班牙語）
危地馬拉
我要去前面的鎮子
能幫我嗎？
進來
來，披上這個
你要去哪兒？
回家
BLONSKY: I've run into bad situations on crap missions before.
我也曾在狗屎任務裏陷入絕境
I've seen good men go down
我也見過優秀的戰士
purely because someone didn't let us know what we were walking into.
因為對任務不瞭解，而白白送命
I've moved on to the next one,because that's what we do, right?
但我總是迎接下一個任務，從不回頭因為這就是我的職責，對吧？
I mean, that's the job.
這就是我的使命
But this?
但這次？
This is a whole new level of weird.
這次可不是一般的詭異
And I don't feel inclined to step away from it.
我完全不想就這麼抽身離去
So if you're taking another crack at him,I want in.
所以如果您還想再次行動，算我一個
And, with respect, you should be looking for a team that's prepped and ready to fight,
還有，恕我直言，下一次您應該讓大家做好充分的準備
because if that thing shows up again,
否則的話，如果那怪物再出現
you're gonna have a lot of professional tough guys pissing in their pants.
您請來的精英們大多都會嚇得尿褲子
Sir.
長官
(HENS CLUCKING)
(DOG BARKING)
恰帕斯，墨西哥
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(COINS CLINKING)
(CHATTERING IN SPANISH)
Tienes mas stretchy?
有更有彈性的嗎？
Yeah. Perfecto.
嗯，很好
(MOTORCYCLE PASSING)
Let me emphasise that what I'm about to share with you
我再重申一次
is tremendously sensitive,both to me personally and the Army.
這事對於我和軍隊來說，都是高度機密的
You're aware that we've got an Infantry Weapons Development programme.
你應該知道我們有一個步兵武器研發計劃
Well, in WWll, they initiated a subprogram
在二戰期間，軍方啟動了一個子計劃
for Bio-Tech Force Enhancement.
用於增強生化科技戰鬥力
Yeah, Super Soldier.
嗯，超級士兵
Yes.
對
An oversimplification, but yes.
簡單來說，就是這個意思
And I dusted it off, got 'em doing serious work again, bold work.
現在，我又重新開始推動這個計劃做一些認真的，勇敢的嘗試
Across the hall,they were trying to arm you better.
他們想做的是把你武裝的更強大
We were tryin' to make you better.
而我們想做的，是讓你變得更強大
Banner's work was very early phase.It wasn't even weapons application.
那時班納的工作還處於起步階段還談不上什麼武器
He thought he was working on radiation resistance.
他以為自己在做抗輻射試驗
I would never have told him what the project really was.
我可不會告訴他這個計劃的真實情況
But he was so sure of what he was onto,that he tested it on himself.
但他過於自信，以至於要拿自己做試驗
And something went very wrong.
而試驗出了很大的問題
Or it went very right.
不過也可以說是無心插柳
As far as I'm concerned, that man's whole body is the property of the US Army.
對我而言，那小子的身體就是屬於美國陸軍的
You said he wasn't working on weapons, right?
您剛才說他不是在做武器試驗？
- No. - But you were. You were, weren't you?
- 對  - 但您是這麼計劃的，是吧？
You were trying other things.
您另有打算
One serum we developed
我們研製的一種血清
was very promising.
很有前景
- So why did he run? - He's a scientist.
- 但他為什麼跑了？ - 他是個科學家
He is not one of us.
跟我們不一樣
- Blonsky, how old are you? 45? - 39.
- 布朗斯基，你幾歲了？45？  - 39
- It takes a toll, doesn't it? - Yes, it does.
- 有點力不從心了吧？  - 沒錯
So get out of the trenches.
那就別再戰鬥了
You should be a Colonel by now,with your record.
從你的檔案看，你現在都該是上校了
No, I'm a fighter.I'll be one for as long as I can.
不，我是個戰士，我會戰鬥到最後一刻
You know, if I could take what I know now,put it in the body I had ten years ago,
知道麼，以我現在的見識加上我十年前的身體
that would be someone I wouldn't want to fight.
那會是一個讓現在的我都恐懼的對手
I could probably arrange something like that.
也許我可以給你這樣的機會
卡爾沃大學，弗吉尼亞
已經17天沒有事故
伊麗莎白·羅斯博士，分子生物學
斯坦利的比薩屋
Take care, kids.
路上小心，孩子們
Stan, I give you my word,
斯坦，我向你保證
whatever you've heard about me,it's not true.
你聽到的任何關於我的消息，都是假的
Oh, I know it. I always knew it.
我知道，我一直都知道
I mean, you know how I felt about you two.
你知道我對你們倆的感情
- Have you talked to her? - No.
- 你和她見面了嗎？  - 沒
She doesn't know that I'm here.
她不知道我在這裏了
- She's with somebody? - Yeah, he's a head shrink.
- 她有男朋友嗎？  - 嗯，一個心理學家
They say he's one of the best.But a really nice guy.
據說學術上很有成就。他的確是個好小伙子
Good. That's good.
好，很好
- Bruce, what can I do to help you? - I could use a bed for a few nights.
- 我能幫你什麼嗎，布魯斯？  - 方便的話我想有張床睡幾天
- You can have the spare room upstairs. - That'd be so great.
- 樓上有空的房間  - 那太好了
There is one other thing.
還有另一件事
Excuse me. Pardon me.
抱歉，借過
Coming through.
借過
Hey, pal. I got a delivery on five.
嘿，哥們，五樓有叫外賣的
I don't think there's anybody up there.
那上面沒人
Oh, man. I'm gonna catch hell if I don't collect. You got to let me try.
噢，我要是沒收到錢會很慘的,請讓我上去看看吧
I'll tell you what. I got an extra medium.Take it on the house.
對了，我多出一塊中號的，拿著吧
- You are the man. - God bless you, brother.
- 真是找對人了  - 上帝保佑你，兄弟
All right.
太好了
(COMPUTERS BLEEPING)
伊麗莎白·羅斯博士
密碼：
Okay.
行了
（伽瑪脈衝）
（沒有結果）
（B·班納）
呼叫藍先生
綠先生！搜索結果如何？
數據沒了
這樣…
我就無能為力了
現在準備怎樣？
還得繼續逃命
We're pretty well closed here, folks.I'm sorry.
要關門了，各位，不好意思
Oh, come on, Stan. It's Friday night.
噢，拜託，斯坦，這可是週五晚上呢
Oh, kids.
是你們啊
I got nothing but marinara now.
現在只有海員沙司（意大利菜）了
Oh, I got to have a Mister Pink, please.
哦，我一定得來一塊紅粉比薩
She worked through dinner again,of course.
她又工作得錯過晚飯了
Stan?
斯坦？
And he... I go, " So, yeah,I mean, where were you?
然後我說，「我的意思是，你在哪裏？」
"I can't... I don't know where you were, Cecil."
「我都不知道你在哪裏，塞西爾」
And he goes, "Not where you been at."
他說，「反正不和你在一起」
I thought, "Oh, my God." I just felt so awful.
「噢，天吶」，我感覺糟透了
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Bruce?
布魯斯？
Betty? What's going on?
貝蒂？怎麼了？
Betty...
貝蒂…
Just tell me if I saw what I think I saw.
告訴我，我看到的是不是真的
- I don't know what to say. - Please, just tell me the truth.
- 我不知道該怎麼跟你說  - 請告訴我真相
BETTY: Don't go. Don't go.
別離開我，別離開我
I want you to come with me now.
我要你跟我回去
Please. Come with me.
求你了，跟我回去
Please.
求你了
BETTY: It's our data.
這就是我們的數據
I got in there before they carted it all away.
我在他們搬東西之前進去拿到的
I hoped somewhere that it might tell us something someday.
我希望哪一天能派上用場
- Does the General know that you have this? - No, I don't think so.
- 將軍知道你拿著這個嗎？  - 我想他不知道
I haven't spoken to him in a couple of years.
我幾年沒和他說話了
You have to be sure.
你要確定
Bruce, I don't understand why we can't just go in there together and talk to him.
布魯斯，我就是不明白,為什麼我們不能一起去和他談談
He told me what he wanted to do.He wants it out of me.
他告訴了我他的意圖,他想從我這裏拿到他想要的東西
He wants to dissect it so that he can replicate it.
他想研究我的身體，這樣他就能夠複製
He wants to make it a weapon.
他想把我變成武器
（斯塔克工業）
- Hi. - Hi.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- I thought you might want to... - Thanks.
- 我想你也許需要…  - 謝謝
Listen, I should leave early,as early as I can.
我該走了，越早越好
Really? You can't stay at all?
真的？就不能留下來？
I want to,but it's just not safe for me to be here.
我也想，但這裏不安全
- If I could borrow some cash... - Of course.
- 如果能借點錢…  - 沒問題
I need to take a bus.
我要坐公車
Well, at least let me walk you to the station.
那就讓我送你去車站
Okay.
好
- You have everything you need? - Yeah.
- 東西都帶齊了？  - 嗯
I...
我…
What?
怎麼？
- Good night. - Good night.
- 晚安  - 晚安
I hope you get some rest.
希望你能休息好
We're giving you a very low dose only.
我們只給你很小的劑量
I need you sharp out there and disciplined.
你要警惕，要遵守紀律
First sign of any side effect,
we stop and you're off team until you straighten out.
一旦有副作用的感覺
我們就停止,你要等到恢復以後再做下次試驗
- Agreed? - Agreed.
- 同意嗎  - 同意
You'll get two separate infusions.
我們會有兩條注射管
One into the deep muscle,one into the bone marrow centres.
一條注射到肌肉深處,一條注射到脊椎中央
The bone ones are going to hurt.
注射到脊髓可能會痛
(GRUNTS)
Is everything okay?
沒事吧？
I think so.
還好
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Come here.
過來
- I just wanna do this. - Oh.
- 我就是想幫你  - 哦
- It's better like that. - Yeah?
- 這樣更好  - 是嗎？
It feels too tight, huh?
太小了一點吧？
- Yeah, a little. - Okay.
- 是有點  - 嗯
- What? - They're here.
- 怎麼？  - 他們來了
- Betty, look at me, look at me! - Bruce!
- 貝蒂，看著我，看著我！  - 布魯斯！
You have to go far away from me as you can!
遠離我，越遠越好！
- Don't argue with me, just go. Go! - Bruce!
- 別問我為什麼，走，快走！  - 布魯斯！
(CAR ALARM SOUNDING)
Damn it! We'd have had snipers on target in three more minutes.
該死！再有三分鐘，狙擊手就能到位了
I wanna know who jumped the gun.
誰這麼毛手毛腳的！
He's heading 2-7-0.
他朝270方向去了
Blonsky! Not yet!
布朗斯基！先別！
Sir.
長官
Look alive. This could get interesting.
小心點，會很有意思的
I got him!
他在這裏！
Stop! Stop!
停下！停下！
I know you're in there!
我知道你在裏面！
General, please!
求你了，將軍！
Sir?
長官？
Dad!
爸爸！
- Dad, please don't do this. - You can't see this clearly. Now, get inside.
- 爸，請別這樣  - 你不明白，給我進去
There he is!
他在那裏！
SOLDIER 1 ON RADIO,Target is in the overpass. We have a visual.
目標在天橋，我們看見了
Do not engage! Repeat, do not engage!
不要交火！重複，不要交火！
SOLDIER 2: He's locked in.
他被困住了
Put two canisters in there with him.
扔兩個催淚彈進去
SOLDIER: Fire!
開火！
Get her back here!
抓她回來！
(GRUNTING)
Now she'll see.
現在她要看到了
(ROARING)
(GROWLING)
Alpha team?
A隊何在？
Let him have all of it.
讓他享受炮火吧
SOLDIER 2: Come on, light him up!
朝他開火！
Where are the fifty cals? Move your asses!
越野戰車在哪裏？趕緊過來！
(GRUNTING)
Oh, my God!
哦，天！
Blonsky, now you're up!
布朗斯基，該你了！
Sir?
長官？
Cover me.
掩護我
(GROWLING)
Remember me?
還記得我嗎？
My God, he's doing it.
天，不錯啊
Move him toward the cannons!
把他往加農炮方向引！
SOLDIER: Move!
快！
(GROWLS)
Hold your position!
原地待命！
BLONSKY: Do it now!
可以了！
(HIGH-PITCHED BUZZING)
(GRUNTING)
Please, please, please, no!
求你了，求你了，不要！
- Please, please, please! - Get her back!
- 求你了，求你了！   - 拉開她！
You're killing him!
你會殺了他的！
BETTY: Stop! Get off of me!
住手！放開我！
(DISTORTED) Bruce!
布魯斯！
Bruce! Bruce!
布魯斯！布魯斯！
Where's the gunship?
武裝直升機呢？
Is that it?
就這樣了？
Blonsky, pull back now.
布朗斯基，回撤！
Pull back!
回撤！
Is that all you got?
你就這麼兩下子？
(GROWLS)
-Fall back! -SOLDIER 3: Fall back! Let's go, let's go!
- 退後！ - 退後！快，快！
GENERAL: Find cover!
找掩護！
Betty!
貝蒂！
Fire, goddamn it!
開火，該死！
Bruce?
布魯斯？
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
Stop firing!
停火！
No!
不！
(GROWLS)
You did the right thing, calling us.
你打電話給我們是對的
I need to know where they're going.
我想知道他們去哪裏了
She'll be in incredible danger as long as she's with him.
只要和他在一起，她的處境就極度危險
From who?
哪來的危險？
He protected her. You almost killed her.
他保護了她，而你差點殺了她
I give you my word, her safety is my main concern at this point.
我向你保證 我現在考慮最多的就是她的安全
You know, it's a point of professional pride with me
知道嗎，幹這行最讓我自豪的
that I can always tell when somebody's lying.
就是能分辨出別人是否在撒謊
And you are.
你就是在撒謊
I don't know where he's going.
我不知道他去哪裏了
-I know she'll help him, if she can. -Then she's aiding a fugitive.
- 我知道她會盡力幫他的  - 那她就是從犯了
And I can't help either one of them.
那樣我可幫不了他們了
I used to wonder why she never talked about you.
我以前不明白為什麼她從不提起你
Now I know!
現在我知道了！
GENERAL: Where does she meet these guys?
她都是在哪裏認識這些人的？
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Bruce?
布魯斯？
Bruce.
布魯斯
(ROARING)
It's okay. It's okay.
沒事了，沒事了
Come here. Come this way.
過來，來這裏
Watch your head.
小心頭
Okay.
好了
We're okay.
我們安全了
It's okay.
沒事了
It's just the rain.
下雨而已
GENERAL: Will he ever walk again?
他還能再走路嗎？
DOCTOR: Most of the bones in his body look like crushed gravel right now.
看起來他大部分骨頭都已經粉碎了
I will say this for him.He's got a heart like a machine.
不過他的心臟堅強的跟機器一樣
Never seen anything like it,outside of a racehorse.
除了賽馬之外，我還從沒見過這樣的
Here.
過來
Okay.
到了
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(BRUCE VOMlTING)
Bruce?
布魯斯？
Oh, hi.
嗨
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
Yeah.
嗯
Yeah, actually, I feel a lot better.
其實呢，已經好很多了
-Good. -I just had to get my data back.
- 很好  - 我只是得把數據拿回來
You ate it?
你吞下去了？
Well, you know, the circumstances called for a little improvisation.
嗯，那種情況下必須急中生智
Wow.
哇
Okay, so they didn't have a great selection,but I got you some options.
我沒找到太好的，不過還是買了一些
First thing's first.
首先
Oh, you're kidding me.
開玩笑吧
What?
怎麼？
-No. -They were the stretchiest pair they had.
- 不行  - 這是他們那裏最有彈性的了
I'll take my chances.
那我只好試試看了
FEMALE REPORTER.; Rumours continue to swirl about a violent clash
關於美軍和不明生物
between forces of the US military and an unknown adversary
今天早些時候在卡爾沃大學交火的傳言
on the campus of Culver University earlier today.
已經愈演愈烈
Sophomores Jack McGhee and Jim Wilson witnessed some of the battle.
二年級學生傑克·麥吉爾和吉姆·威爾遜,目擊了部分戰鬥場面
JIM.; It was so big.
真的很大
-It was like this huge, like, hulk! -Yeah.
- 就像是浩克一樣！  - 對
FEMALE REPORTER.; McGhee, who happens to be a reporter for the campus paper,
麥吉爾正好是校報的記者
captured this on his cell phone.
他用手機拍下了畫面
Further search for the mysterious ''hulk''
關於這個神秘「浩克」的搜尋工作
was postponed by powerful thunderstorms in the Smoky Mountain National Forest.
由於煙山國家森林公園的暴風雨而推遲
Not too short back there.
後面別太短
I have done this before, you know.
我以前也是幫你剪過的，記得麼
I don't know how you've done this on your own for all this time.
不知道這麼些年你一個人是怎麼過來的
With clippers, usually.
一般是用大剪刀
(BETTY CHUCKLING)
(WATCH BEEPING)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
-Wait, wait, wait. Wait. -What? What?
- 等等，等等 - 怎麼？
We can't do this.
還是別做了
-It's okay. I want to. -No.
- 沒事的，我想要  - 不行
No.
不
I can't .
不行
(BEEPING SLOWS)
I can't get too excited.
我不能太興奮
(BEEPING STOPS)
Not even a little excited?
一點點也不行？
(BRUCE SlGHS)
BETTY: It's okay.
好吧
Sir, it's Blonsky.
先生，是布朗斯基的事
Has anyone found out if he has next of kin or family?
能聯繫到他的家屬嗎？
Ask him yourself.
您自己問他吧
Sir?
長官？
-Good to see you back on your feet, soldier. -Thank you, sir.
- 看到你恢復很高興，戰士  - 謝謝，長官
How do you feel?
感覺如何？
Pissed off and ready for round three.
很生氣，準備第三波戰鬥
Basically, we can't use any of this,because they can track all of it.
基本上這些都不能帶  因為他們都能跟蹤到
Well, my lip gloss? Can they track that?
唇膏呢？也能跟蹤到？
-No. You can take your lip gloss. -Thank you.
- 不會，你可以帶著  - 謝謝
-Well, I need my glasses. -Well, you can take
- 我還要眼鏡  - 行，也可以帶著
-your glasses and your watch, okay? -Okay.
- 眼鏡和手錶，好嗎？ - 嗯
We can use most of it. We just can't use the credit cards, the ID or the phone.
除了信用卡，身份證和手機 其他都能帶
-Don't even turn that on. -Okay.
- 手機別開機 - 好
And we'll take the cash, obviously.
還要帶現金
How will we get where we need to go on $40 and no credit cards?
只帶四十塊錢，又沒有信用卡 能去哪裏？
Well, we could sell this.
那，可以賣掉這個
No. No, that's the only thing you have left from her. No.
不行，這是你母親留給你的唯一的東西了
Well, we'll have to try and get it back.
那我們得試著再贖回來了
SPARR: Federal is already monitoring phones,
聯邦調查局已經在監控通話
plastic and Dr Ross's web accounts,
信用卡，以及羅斯博士的網絡賬號
and local PD have been placed on alert.
當地警局也已處於警備狀態
They'll pop up somewhere and when they do, it comes straight to us.
一旦他們出現，消息會直接傳到我們這裏
GENERAL: They're not gonna just pop up.
他們不會突然出現的
He made it five years and got across borders without making any mistakes.
他花了五年時間 神不知鬼不覺的越過了邊境
He's not gonna use a damn credit card now.
他現在可不會用什麼信用卡
If he was trying to escape, he'd be long gone.
他要是想逃，那早走了
He's not trying to escape this time.
現在他不是想逃走
He's looking for help and that's how we're gonna get him.
他正在尋求幫助，這才是我們的線索
We know what they're after and we know he's been talking to somebody.
我們知道他們要的是什麼 我們也知道他一直在和人聯繫
You all have copies of the correspondence.
你們都有通信的備份
The aliases Mr Green and Mr Blue
綠先生和藍先生的聯絡
have been added to the SHIELD Operations Database.
已經納入了神盾數據庫的監控
If he comes up for air, we'll be waiting.
我們只要守株待兔，等他們再聯繫
（藍先生，附上數據，是時候見面了綠先生）
If he makes a peep, we'll hear him.
只要他有動靜，我們就能知道
And when he slips up, we'll be ready.
而他冒出來的時候，我們將會等著他
（國土戰略干預組·後勤部）
（藍先生，附上數據，是時候見面了綠先生）
（格雷本學院）
（細胞生命系）
（塞繆爾·史登博士）
（匹配數據）
（塞繆爾·史登博士，紐約市）
Hey.
嘿
Smile.
笑一個
What is it like?
那是什麼樣的感覺？
When it happens, what do you experience?
變身的時候，什麼感覺？
Remember those experiments we volunteered for at Harvard?
記得我們在哈佛的時候 自願參加的那些試驗嗎？
Those induced hallucinations?
誘發幻覺試驗？
It's a lot like that,just a thousand times amplified.
很像那個，只不過放大了一千倍
It's like someone's poured a litre of acid into my brain.
我的腦子裏就像被倒入了一升的酸
-Do you remember anything? -Just fragments. Images.
- 還記得什麼嗎？  - 一些碎片，圖像
There's too much noise.I can never derive anything out of it.
干擾太多，實在記不起什麼了
-But then it's still you inside it. -No. No, it's not.
- 但那終歸是你  - 不，不是了
I don't know.In the cave, I really felt like it knew me.
我不知道，在洞穴的時候 我真的感覺它認識我
Maybe your mind is in there,
也許你的心還在那裏
it's just overcharged and can't process what's happening.
只是過載了，無法正常處理形勢了
I don't want to control it.I want to get rid of it.
我不想控制它，我想擺脫它
Are you ready?
準備好了嗎？
Let's even the playing field a little.
讓我們把戰鬥變得更公平些
Gentlemen.
先生們
(HORN BLARING)
BETTY: Bruce, wake up.There's something going on.
布魯斯，醒醒，有狀況
（請準備停車）
（前方檢查）
We got to go. Walk toward the back.Just don't move too fast.
我們得走了，慢慢往後，別太快
All right. Come.
好了，來
BETTY: It is a long way uptown.I think the subway's probably quickest.
到郊區還很遠，坐地鐵會比較快
Me in a metal tube, deep underground,
你讓我在世上最擁擠的城市和數百人一起
with hundreds of people in the most aggressive city in the world?
擠在地下的鐵罐子裏？
Right. Let's get a cab.
好吧，打車
CAB DRlVER: Come on, now! Let's go!You're too slow! You drive like a woman!
上路啦！你們開得這麼慢，跟娘們似的！
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
-Very nice. You see her? -Oh, my.
- 真漂亮，看到她的表情沒？  - 噢天
Very pretty. Watch out, you goat!
很好，小心，白癡！
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
呼吸，呼吸
Are you out of your mind?
你瘋了嗎？
-What is wrong with you? -What's the matter, baby?
- 你怎麼了？  - 怎麼了，寶貝？
You don't like a good ride?
不喜歡我的風格？
(GRUNTING)
Asshole!
混蛋！
(BETTY GRUNTS)
You know, I know a few techniques could help you
我知道一些技巧，可以幫你有效的
-manage that anger very effectively. -You zip it. We're walking.
- 控制怒氣  - 閉嘴，走路
Okay.
好吧
Excuse me. Dr Sterns?
打擾了，史登博士？
-Yes. -I'm sorry to bother you. I'm Elizabeth Ross.
- 是我  - 不好意思打擾了，我是伊麗莎白·羅斯
Oh! Dr Ross!
哦！羅斯博士！
-I have someone who'd like to meet you. -Okay.
- 我想為您引見一個人  - 好
It's Mr Blue, isn't it?
藍先生，是你嗎？
Mr Green?
綠先生？
I got to tell you,I've been wondering if you were even real.
告訴你，我曾經都懷疑你的存在
And if you were, what would it look like?
我想如果你不是虛擬的，那會是什麼樣？
A person with that much power lurking in him.
身上潛伏著那麼巨大的能量
Nothing could have surprised me more
想不到真的能在現實中和你握手
than this unassuming man shaking my hand.
這真是太讓人太驚喜了
But, look. We're not strolling into the park for a picnic, here.
不過我們可不是要過家家
Even if everything goes perfectly,
即使一切順利
if we induce an episode,if we get the dosage exactly right,
即使我們能讓你變身，而且控制好劑量
is that going to be a lasting cure
但那會是持久有效的治癒
or just some antidote to suppress that specific flare-up?
還是只是暫時的抑制呢？
I don't know.
不得而知了
What I'm saying is that if we overshoot this by even the smallest integer
我的意思是，即使多出這麼一點點劑量
we're dealing with concentrations with extraordinary levels of toxicity.
那裏面濃縮的也是多得驚人的毒素
-You mean it could kill him. -Kill him? Yeah. I should say so.
- 你是說會害死他  - 害死他？對，是這個意思
You should know that there's a flip side to this, too.
還有另一種情況
If we miss on the low side,if we induce me and it fails,
如果劑量少了 如果我變身了而治療又失敗了
this will be very dangerous for you.
那你可就危險了
Look. I've always been more curious than cautious,
聽著，我行事一向以好奇心驅使多過謹慎
and that's served me pretty well.So, are we going to do this?
不過到目前為止還沒出過什麼事 那我們到底做不做試驗？
How you feeling, man?
感覺如何，夥計？
Like a monster.
像野獸一樣
Okay. On the table.
好吧，上桌子
These will protect you from yourself if you have a strong reaction.
如果反應劇烈，這些能就你
You can tell me later if you thought it was strong.
你可以事後再告訴我反應是否劇烈
Oh, come on! Stupid graduate students.
噢，不是吧！那幫白癡研究生
Okay...
好的…
You, you, you.
這個，這個，還有這個
This will be a somewhat novel sensation.
這將會是從未有過的奇妙體驗
(MACHINE STARTING UP)
We have begun.
開始了
The dialysis machine will mix the antidote with your blood.
透析機會把解毒藥和你的血液混合
Except the antidote will only take hold once we've achieved a full reaction.
只不過解毒藥要等到完全反應時 才能加入
Just relax.
放鬆吧
Okay. We are comprehensive.
好了，進入狀態了
Here you go.
這個給你
All right. We set to pop?
好了，準備好了嗎？
I'd take your hands off him.
換我就不會抓他手
(GRUNTING)
Oh, my God!
噢天！
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Wait, wait! There's more! Wait!
等等！還有！等等！
-Now. Okay, now! -STERNS: Wait.
- 現在可以了，快！  - 等等
Now, do it! Do it!
趕緊！快點！
Bruce! Bruce, look at me.
布魯斯！布魯斯，看著我
Stay with me. The antidote, now!Sterns, do it now!
挺住，趕緊加解毒藥！史登，快點！
Bruce, look at me. Look in my eyes.Please, look in my eyes.
布魯斯，看著我，看著我的眼睛 求你了，看著我的眼睛
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Oh, you've got to be kidding me!
開玩笑吧！
(HULK GROANING)
Bruce.
布魯斯
Oh, my God.
噢天
Bruce? Bruce, can you hear me?
布魯斯？布魯斯，能聽到我說話嗎？
Bruce?
布魯斯？
(GASPS)
It's okay. You're okay. You're okay.
沒事了，沒事了
You did it.
你挺過來了
He's fine. This is fantastic.
他沒事了，太奇妙了
BETTY: It's over.
結束了
Hi.
嗨
That was the most extraordinary thing I have seen in my entire life!
這是我這輩子見過的最不可思議的情景！
Okay, you know what? Stop, please.
你消停一下吧，求你了
We need to go back and talk about what just happened in there.
我們得談談剛才發生的事
Absolutely. Okay. The gamma pulse came from the amygdala.
顯然伽瑪脈衝來自扁桃腺
-I think Dr Ross's primer... -Are you okay?
- 我想羅斯博士的核酸合成引物… - 你還好吧？
...lets the cells absorb the energy temporarily, and then it abates.
使得細胞暫時吸收了能量，然後又減弱
That's why you didn't die of radiation sickness years ago!
這就是你數年前沒有死於輻射的原因！
Now, maybe we've neutralised those cells permanently,
現在，也許我們已經永久的 幹掉這些細胞了
or maybe we just suppressed that event.
但也許只是暫時抑制住了
I'm inclined to think the latter,but it's hard to know
我傾向於後者，但目前還不好說
because none of our test subjects ever survived.
因為我們的試驗樣本都沒有生還
-Of course, they weren't getting the primer! -Wait, wait.
- 當然了，因為它們沒有核酸合成引物… - 等等
-Wait, what did you just say? -They weren't getting
- 等等，你剛才說什麼？ - 他們沒有
-the myostatin primer... -No, no, no. Test subjects?
- 肌肉抑制素核酸合成引物 - 不是，試驗樣本？
What test subjects?
什麼試驗樣本？
Come with me.
跟我來
-SPARR: What's the activity level? -Snipers are covering Alpha sector.
- 情況如何？ - 狙擊手已經能覆蓋A區了
STERNS ON RADIO.;We started on rats and mice,
我們從小白鼠下手
but it just compIeteIy fried them,so we had to go bigger.
不過試驗一開始它們就被烤焦了 所以我們得找大點的動物
And we still don't know which is more toxic,the gamma or your blood.
我們還不清楚，伽瑪和你的血液 哪個更具毒性
-What do you mean, my blood? -Bruce, this is all you.
- 我的血液？什麼意思？ - 布魯斯，這些都是你的
You didn't send me much to work with,so I had to concentrate it and make more.
你沒給我寄太多，所以我只好通過濃縮 製造更多樣本
With a little more trial and error,there's no end to what we can do!
通過試錯法，這個試驗將潛力無窮
This is potentially Olympian!
多麼偉大的工程！
This gamma technology has limitless applications.
伽瑪技術的應用前景很廣
We'll unlock hundreds of cures.
數百種治病方法將誕生
We will make humans impervious to disease!
人類從此將免受疾病困擾！
No, no, we've got to destroy it.
不行，我們得毀了它們
-Wait, what? -All of it.
- 等等，什麼？ - 全部
Tonight. We're gonna incinerate it.
今晚我們就得把它們都毀了
-Is this the whole supply? -What...
- 這是總開關？ - 等等…
We could get the Nobel for this!
我們可以因此得到諾貝爾！
You don't understand the power of this thing.
你不明白這東西的威力
It is too dangerous. It cannot be controlled.
這太危險了，我們無法控制
At your discretion, shooter.
狙擊手，自行掌握開槍時機
STERNS ON RADIO.; ...three of us!This is Promethean fire!
…我們三個！這是普羅米修斯之火啊（意為將開創生物學新時代）
BRUCE ON RADIO.; It's just...
但是…
SOLDIER ON RADIO.; No shot.
無法瞄準
Blonsky's going in.
布朗斯基進去了
GENERAL.; Blonsky, stand down.My daughter's in there!
布朗斯基，別衝動，我女兒在裏面！
We have the antidote now.
我們已經有解毒藥了
They don't want the antidote!They want to make it a weapon!
他們要的不是解毒藥！他們想製造武器！
(SIRENS WAlLING)
And if we let it go, we will never get it back.
這事會變得一發不可收拾
You don't know how powerful this thing is.
你不知道這東西的威力
I hate the government just as much as anyone,
我和別人一樣痛恨政府
but you're being a little paranoid,don't you think?
但你不覺得自己有點偏執了？
(GASPS)
Bruce! Bruce!
布魯斯！布魯斯！
Get out.
出去
(BETTY SCREAMS)
Where is it? Come on, where is it?
它在哪裏？快點，它在哪裏？
(BRUCE EXCLAIMS)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Show him to me.
讓它出現吧
Blonsky!
布朗斯基！
(HEART BEATING SLOWLY)
SOLDIER: Miss!
小姐！
Take this.
披著這個
If you took it from me, I'm gonna put you in a hole for the rest of your life.
你相信不相信 我要你這輩子生不如死
Betty.
貝蒂
I will never forgive what you've done to him.
我這輩子都不會原諒你對他的所作所為
He's a fugitive.
你為了掩蓋你的失敗，保住你的烏紗
You made him a fugitive
才讓他成了逃犯
to cover your failures and to protect your career.
而讓他變成逃犯的
Don't ever speak to me as your daughter again.
別再當我是你女兒了
It's only because you're my daughter that you're not in handcuffs, too.
你要不是我女兒，現在也已經被銬上了
SPARR: Are you telling me you can make more like him?
你是說你還能造出更多那樣的怪獸？
No! Not yet. I sorted out a few pieces,but it's not like I can put together
不！還沒，我只是明白了一點點,但還遠不清楚具體細節
the same Humpty Dumpty,if that's what you're asking.
你說的那種矮胖子，我怎麼可能造得出來
He was a freak accident!The goal is to do it better!
他是詭異的意外的產物 我們能做的只是讓它更強
So Banner's the only...
那麼只有班納一個…
-She's an annoying bitch. -Why are you always hitting people?
- 這婊子真囉嗦  - 你為什麼老是打人？
Now what possibly could I have done to deserve such aggression?
憑什麼你又這樣對我？
It's not what you've done.It's what you're gonna do.
不是你做了什麼，而是我要你做什麼
I want what you got out of Banner.I want that.
我要你把我變成班納那樣
You look like you've got a little something in you already, don't you?
看樣子你體內已經有了點什麼，是吧？
I want more.You've seen what he becomes, right?
還不夠，你見過他變身的樣子吧？
I have.
是的
And it's beautiful.
太美妙了
Godlike.
神僊一樣
Well, I want that.
那好，我要的就是那個
I need that. Make me that.
我需要變成那樣，讓我變成那樣
I don't know what you've got inside you already.
我不知道你體內已經有了什麼
The mix could be
搞不好可能變成
an abomination.
憎惡
(GASPlNG) I didn't say I was unwilling.
我沒說我不願意
I just need informed consent.
我只是想讓你充分知情而已
And you've given it.
現在不就行了麼
（綠先生，強度：14.36%）
This is what I was trying to explain.
我想要和你解釋的就是這個
I don't know what you've been ladling into yourself.
我不知道你把你自己怎麼了
But clearly it worked.
不過顯然起作用了
Let's assume you don't understand a word I'm saying,
假設你聽不懂我說的話
but if you'll just get back on the table,
但如果你回到桌子上
I can fix this.
我能把你治好
(ABOMINATION GROWLING)
(ABOMINATION LAUGHlNG)
SOLDIER 1 : Shoot it! SOLDIER 2: Hey!
- 開槍！  - 嗨！
No!
不！
(SOLDIERS SCREAMlNG)
SOLDIER 5: Delta 4 to Leader.
D4小隊報告
They took out two of our guys,two of our guys!
他們幹掉了我們兩個人，兩個人！
Blonsky and the Major are still inside!
布朗斯基和少校還在裏面！
(ABOMINATION GROWLING)
Come on! Move, move, move, move!
快點！快，快，快！
It's over there!
就在那裏！
SOLDIER 2: Drop them!
放開他們！
SOLDIER 3: What is that thing? SOLDIER 4: Shoot it!
- 那是什麼？  - 開火！
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Okay. All right! You... You, drive!Let's go! Move, move!
好吧！你…你來開車！我們走！走！
SOLDIER 5: Delta 4 to Leader!SOLDIER 6: Go, go, go, go, go!
- D4小隊報告！ - 行動！行動！
SOLDIER 5: Something big just went off down here!
一個大怪物剛從上面下來！
General, you should hear this!
將軍，你聽聽這個！
The Hulk is in the street!I repeat, the Hulk is in the street!
浩克在街上！重複，浩克在街上！
That's impossible.You get a hold of yourself, young man.
不可能，你先照顧好自己，年輕人
You get it together. What is your position?
先穩住，你的位置是？
121st Street, heading north on Broadway!
121街，往北開向百老匯！
Turn us around.
回頭
We're going back. Why are we going back?
回頭了，為什麼要回頭？
Damn it! Give me eyes down there!
該死！給我圖像！
Yes, sir!
遵命，長官！
What the hell was that?
那他媽的是什麼？
Go, go, go!
行動，行動！
(SIRENS WAlLING)
No!
不！
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
One of yours?
你的人？
Oh, my God. What have you done?
老天，你都幹了什麼？
OFFlCER: Fire at him, fire at him!
朝他開火，朝他開火！
Do you think a rifle's gonna hurt that?
你覺得步槍能傷到它？
Come on!
來吧！
Sweet.
爽
(ABOMINATION ROARING)
Booyah!
耶！
(LAUGHING)
(CAR ALARMS BEEPING)
Get out of there, soldier!
快跑，士兵！
Stacy!
斯黛西！!
Give me a real fight!
讓我痛快打一架！
Sir?
長官？
Tell them to bring everything they've got and head for Harlem.
讓他們帶上所有東西，還有頭盔
It has to be me.You have to take me back there.
得我上，你得帶我回去
What are you saying?
你說什麼？
You think you can control it?
你覺得你能搞定？
No, no, not control it,but, I don't know, maybe aim it.
不，不是搞定，不知道，盡力吧
And what if you can't ?
如果失敗了呢？
We made this thing.
這是我們造成的局面
All of us.
我們所有人
Please.
拜託了
-Land us near it. -No, no. No, keep us high.
- 在附近降落 - 不，這個高度就可以了
Open the back door.
開後艙門
Bruce! Bruce, stop!Stop! What are you doing?
布魯斯！布魯斯，別！停下！你幹嘛？
Think about this!You don't even know if you'll change!
想想看！你都不一定能變身！
You don't have to do this!Please, this is insane!
你沒必要這樣！求你了，別傻了！
Betty, I've got to try.
貝蒂，我得試試
I'm sorry.
對不起
Oh, shit!
該死！
-Get her in here! -Come on, miss.
- 拉她進來！ - 來吧，小姐
(HULK GROWLING)
There. Betty!
在那裏，貝蒂！
(PEOPLE CLAMOURING)
(ROARING)
Hulk!
浩克！
Yeah!
(BOTH GROWLING)
(ABOMINATION LAUGHING)
Come on!
來吧！
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
(ROARING)
Is that all you've got?
你就這兩下子？
Use that thing, soldier! Give him some help!
用那個，士兵！給他點幫助！
Which one?
幫哪個？
Help the green one, damn it!Which one do you think?
綠色的那個，白癡！你以為呢？
Cut the other one in half!
把另一個做掉！
Ross!
羅斯！
Keep it on him!
跟住他！
(HULK AND ABOMINATION GRUNTING)
PlLOT: Look, I got to put it down! GENERAL: Hang on!
- 我得降落了！ - 挺住！
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(ABOMINATION AND HULK GRUNTING)
Dad?
爸爸？
(GROANING)
Are you hurt? Let me help you.
你疼嗎？我來幫你
I'm all right. Just find a way out.
我沒事，找路出去先
(GROWLING)
(CHUCKLING)
You don't deserve this power!Now watch her die!
你不配這種力量！看著她死吧！
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Look out!
小心！
General?
將軍？
Any last words?
還有遺言嗎？
Hulk smash!
浩克斬！
(ROARING)
BETTY: Stop!
住手！
(ROARING)
It's okay.
沒事了
Betty.
貝蒂
(GROWLING)
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
（電量低）
（貝拉·庫拉，英屬哥倫比亞）
（貝蒂·羅斯，卡爾沃大學）
(HEART BEATING)
(HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
已經31天沒有事故發生
已經0天沒有事故發生
GENERAL: Reload.
加滿
Reload.
TONY: The smell of stale beer and defeat.
瞧你這垂頭喪氣的樣子
You know, I hate to say,"I told you so," General,
我不喜歡說「早跟你說過」之類的話，將軍
but that Super Soldier programme was put on ice for a reason.
但那個超級士兵計劃 不是無緣無故被凍結的
I've always felt hardware was more reliable.
我一直覺得硬體更加可靠一些
-Stark. -General.
- 斯塔克  - 將軍
You always wear such nice suits.
你總是穿得這麼整齊
Touche.
說的沒錯
-I hear you have an unusual problem. -You should talk.
- 聽說你有點麻煩？  - 請指教
You should listen.
聽好了
What if I told you we were putting a team together?
不如我們組織一支隊伍？
Who's " we" ?
「我們」？